<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SmartBelt Ultimate</string>

    <string name="Privacy_Text">
        This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use and share your information on our web pages, SMS, APIs, email notifications,
        buttons, widgets, advertisements, commerce services and in our other services linked to this Policy (called collectively the and how our
        partners and third parties do it. For example, you send us information when you use our Services through the Internet, SMS or an
        application such as Twitter for Mac, Twitter for Android or TweetDeck. By using any of our Services, you consent to the collection,
        transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
        This includes any information you choose to provide that is considered confidential under applicable law.
        Whichever country you reside in, you authorize us to transfer, store and use your information in Mexico and in any other country
        in which we operate. In some of these countries, data protection and privacy laws and regulations on when government authorities
        can access data may differ from those in the country in which you live.
        We collect the content and other information you provide when you use the Services, including information about yourself and others,
        such as the data you provide when creating an account and the content you create or provide through the App, including photos
    </string>

    <string name="Privacy_Text2">
        Communication.  We use the information we have, including your contact information, to communicate with
        you regarding our Services, to send you marketing messages that we believe may be of interest to you, and to inform
        you of our products, services, policies and conditions.  We also use the information we have to respond to you when you contact us.
    </string>

    <string name="Privacy_Text3">
        Promote safety and security.  It is important to clarify that we use the information we have to promote security and protection
        in our Services and to investigate the use of our Services, including any suspicious activity or possible violations of our
        Conditions and policies.
    </string>

    <string name="Information_Text">
        La aplicaci칩n esta dise침ada para las personas con enfermedades degenerativas de alta prioridad como podrian ser: Cancer, Alzheimer,
        Diabetes, etc. Ya que estas enfermedades requieren la supervici칩n de las personas a cargo de ellas (Cuidadores), para conocer
        el estado de la persona, asi como su ubicaci칩n para evitar accidentes y mejorar asi el estilo de vida tanto de las Familiares
        como para las personas que padecen dicha enfermedad
    </string>

<<<<<<< HEAD
     Promote safety and security.  It is important to clarify that we use the information we have to promote security and protection in our Services and to investigate the use of our Services, including any suspicious activity or possible violations of our Conditions and policies.</string>
    <string name="Info_App">

Smart Belt is a tool that aims to assist families and geriatric caregivers in the supervision and care of people of the third age or with chronic and severe diseases that require it.

Smart Belt is an app linked to the special Smart Belt belt, in order for the person in charge / caregiver to carry out all the settings, records, administration and supervision of their functions, including: personal account management , medical history log, medication log and administration, pending medical studies and inquiries, scheduled alarms and reminders, belt location map display, and general system settings.
</string>

=======
>>>>>>> 71011cf47c0ecd22ee908cd6f83f6de154526bd3
</resources>

